Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The hate within brings colors of our own.
Oh, yeah.
King has just been defeated. What?
We've defeated the Toby Robo
and the lead performers.
This is getting quite
serious but
it's not over
there are still two
monsters out there who can
stop the Straw Hats it
would take a miracle to
defeat but they've come
this far the struggle
The battle between Luffy and
Kaido grows in intensity, however,
the battle may have an
unexpected consequence.
If Kaido is defeated, his
flame clouds will disappear.
This will cause Onigashima to crash,
and the explosives in its basement
will destroy the entire capital.
Then the tens of thousands
of helpless citizens
enjoying the Fire Festival
will be incinerated.
You're not touching the flower capital!
Go back where you belong!
To make matters worse, Kanjuro
crafted a massive flame monster.
This manifestation of the Kurozumi
Clan's grudge heads toward
the castle basements threatening
to detonate its entire arsenal.
Unless Yamato can stop it.
I knew he'd be here.
That fire monster will
show up any second now.
And Roki's blocking the entrance.
I don't have time to
get in a fight and grab
the key from him and
pull that massive lever.
Fuga!
Can you cover me, Fuga?
Fuga! Fuga!
Ha-ha! Yay!
Thanks a bunch, Fuga!
Fuga!
You keep Rookie busy for me, okay?
Fuga! Rocky!
Hey!
That doesn't look good.
Our bodies back together.
I mean, that's a relief, but how
the hell does that even work?
We need to get both of you
to chop her right away.
There they are!
It's the Straw Hats!
Don't let them escape!
Let's go!
Take them down!
We got enough problems to deal with!
Go away!
How do you like my skull bomb grass?
Get him!
That guy's got a bounty of 200 million!
Guess this is our lucky day!
I'm so dead! Help!
If the bad guys don't get
me, then the fire will!
Just go, Sir Usopp.
You must save Kiku.
Leave me behind.
No, Master Keen.
I won't make it.
Leave me here.
Okay, I'll leave you both and
get out of here on my own!
And why did I even bother coming here?!
You stupid suicidal samurai!
Chipping with honor is still dying!
Don't sacrifice yourself
to take responsibility!
I know that's your culture,
but I don't like it one bit!
I'll survive crawling with
snot dripping out of my nose!
If that's what it takes, it's worth it!
Usopp!
If I die with dignity, then
who'd be here to help you?
Forgive me, sir Usopp.
Just holding on the rain
shouldn't be enough for you!
You have to live!
Ah!
I did!
Listen to him, you two!
Take cover!
What the hell is Izo doing here?
Did we piss off Whitebeard's
old crew somehow?
He's an ex-captain.
And it's not just him.
Marco was here, too.
Why are they after us?
Oh, thank you, whoever you are.
Esau.
I lost again. I'm sorry.
That's enough.
You'll open your walls.
We can catch up as much as we want
later once our country is free.
I can't.
It's over for me.
As your brother, I won't
allow you to give up.
Understand?
Yes.
I'll get you out of here
no matter what it takes.
So live.
Keep fighting.
If you truly believe in straw
hat luffy then you must survive,
right?
Thank you, big brother.
You too.
Please don't die.
Thank God, Usopp!
Yeah?
Wait, you know who I am?
Of course I do!
You're the Sniper King!
Take care of those two! You got it!
You ready, Hamlet? Of
course! Let's go! And away!
It's time to depart on a new journey!
You're dead!
No one passes through! Got it?
You cut fire first!
I've won!
Now undo the paralysis, Jutsu! It's over!
Why don't you undo yours first?
I'll be fine!
I see.
You're a fool!
Stubborn to the bitter end!
But your Jutsu will be undone
once you burn to death!
I saw the fires Lord Odin faced!
This is but a summer breeze in comparison!
I feel like I'm in a dream.
Komurasaki is alive and the fools
on this island will soon be dead.
It's literally music to my ears.
What's taking you so long, Fukurokuju?
We need to get out of here
before this place explodes.
My lord, is anything the matter?
Oh no, just thinking.
Say, while we're here, why
not play that song for me?
You know the one.
It's my favorite.
I haven't heard it in ages.
Yes, of course
They got drake.
let's fuck it in b!
We got no reason to fight those guys!
Sorry, Snake.
Tough luck, Drake.
That was a nuisance and
a waste of our time.
They're quite strong.
Seems Apu ran away.
Do you have Nico Robin in custody yet?
It's in progress.
We were interrupted.
Well, hurry up.
We need to get out of this castle.
All the lead performers were defeated.
Impossible!
The worst generation is still
fighting an uphill battle,
but if they manage to pull this off,
it'll be quite the story indeed.
There will be a massive upset
in the balance of power,
one that would fan the flames of every
little fire we're trying
to put out right now.
What happens at the end of this battle
will set the course for our next age.
That's certainly true.
But what then?
Is mankind even capable of more than this?
All right, go, go, go!
Try that again!
No! No! No! No!
Kosarki!
Now, GumGum!
If I hear GumGum one more time...
Better get used to it!
Rockside!
I'm starting to have some fun.
Ah, so am I.
One more round!
Haven't you had enough already?
Take it easy!
U .A .R.
We get to drink one day a year!
I'm gonna catch it up today!
Just let me have my fun.
It's back to suffering after this.
Screw you, Arachis!
Will you cut it out?
Public officials could
be watching us right now!
Hey, look.
They're setting up the skyships.
The festival's about to wrap up.
Wow!
Look at all the lanterns!
Write down a wish to your ancestors.
They'll see it up in heaven.
I know just what to wish for!
Here.
Go ahead and write one.
It'll come true?
It's really that easy?
You know why they call them sky ships?
Because they go all the way to heaven beyond
the sky, where our lost loved ones are.
You really think Daddy's
gonna read my wish?
Yes, he'll be happy to see it.
Hey, why are you boozing it up right now?
We're fighting!
Cause I'm having a good time.
Everyone is drinking.
It's the fire festival in the capital.
We were supposed to have a party on
Onigashima too until you screwed that up.
Now do you want some or what?
You don't have a care in the world.
Do you tell me you're drunk already?
This is just a little sip.
I ain't drunk.
Why are you so mean to me?
I worked so hard on this
party and you ruined it!
I knew it!
You're drunk off your ass!
What's wrong with letting loose a bitch?
Now, watch!
Oops! Come on!
You can't even stand!
How are you supposed
to fight me like that?!
I kick your ass!
You better not use this as an excuse!
You're so funny!
I'll make myself weak
and all. Take a hint.
I'm showing you that I accept you.
Uh...
Gum-Gum!
Drunken Dragon Blah Blah!
I'm really feeling it now.
I acknowledge your strength, Strahd.
You're the first person who's been able
to go toe-to-toe with me in a long time.
Wiping hammer!
What do I do?
Look at this place what
a mess everything's
ruined I've been having fun going
wild but Now my castle's all screwed up
look at me I can't even save my own home
What do I even do?
What do I do?
We gotta start from scratch.
It took five whole years to
build this place, you know.
Stupid drunk!
That hit really hurt! Damn it!
Are you just pretending to
be drunk or what I started
my own business sold
weapons all over the place
i even made the world's
strongest army With smile
fruits i did my best but
it still wasn't good enough
That was a stupid mistake i
let my guard down not this time
Maybe this is the sign I
should just call it quits.
This is rich and all.
Out of candy line!
Dragon Twister Demolition Brass!
He is all over the place!
No! I'm done! I'm done! Leave me alone!
Where the hell are you going?
Far away!
I'm useless!
Everything I've done takes a crap!
I need to be alone right now!
Don't look at me!
Sorry, but it's too late for you to cry!
You don't want to leave me alone?
Enter!
Mock!
Okay, you drunk, take that!
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Aaaaaah!
His Haki keeps getting stronger!
I like getting drunk, okay?
Stop trying this over me!
Oh!
Uh!
Ah! Ah! Come back!
Find that!
Rock that land!
Dragon's land!
Rock
that
land!
No!
No! No!
This year's reverie has
been a cursed affair.
The Seven Warlords of the
Sea program was abolished.
The situation with Alabasta
was most unfortunate.
And the Revolutionary Army
invaded the Holy Land.
There's no point in lamenting it now.
Indeed.
The land of Wano is our
most pressing concern.
This battle has certainly had more
twists and turns than expected.
This is our best opportunity to strike.
We can't delay.
They'll catch Nico Robin somehow.
With Kaido and Big Mom there,
death could come for anyone.
It's an excuse to wipe
out our inconveniences.
We will erase them all.
And most importantly,
we'll erase the existence of that
Devil Fruit before it's too late.
Maintain combat readiness
until further notice.
All ships remain on standby.
Sir?
What is it?
Not sure.
It looks like a giant shadow. A shadow?
What do you mean?
I have no idea, sir. What?
We'll figure it out!
It's an island.
No, it's unthinkable.
Even to those who know the truth,
it's hardly more than a legend now.
It hasn't awakened for centuries.
You think we still have cause to fear it?
The world government gave it another name
that is proof that the fruit is a threat.
There's only one reason
someone would do such a thing?
To hide its name from
history, it must be erased.